personal changelog for mod "MD2 deep storage"

- 05/01/2018

	- added short description of DSU to about file
	- removed shadows static
	- added edge shadows true

- 11/01/2018

	- made deepstorage prerequisite of each other in research

- 12/01/2018

	- used extended storage code as workaround (now requires extended storage mod to work)
	- added a few more storage categories to deep storage (foodraw, hay, kibble, pemican, stonechunks)

- 20/01/2018

	- added modsync